slingfile.com 2012-12-28

# SlingFile.com - Privacy Policy

**In a nutshell** :

  * We don't send anything illegal:random files are subject to spot checks.
  * We will not spam you and not sell your e-mail address.
  * We will use high-tech security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized users.

SlingFile.com is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. We have prepared this privacy policy to give you full confidence to use this site, and to explain to our users what type of information we collect, how we use that information, and the steps we take to ensure the security of their information.

This privacy policy is only effective for this site, and not to any other web sites that you may be able to access from this site, each of which may have their own information collection, storage, and use policies; which may be different from this site's privacy policy. 

By using this site, you clearly agree to all the points listed in this privacy policy. This privacy policy is effective as of 1 May 2010.

## 1\. What Sort of Information is Collected

**(a) Traffic Data**

We automatically collect anonymous information; referred to as "Traffic Data", when you visit this site. This information does not provide your personal identification but is useful for improving your experience on this site. This information includes (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing this site; and (iv) types of web browsers used to access this site, (v) cookies (to personalize content particular to your interests, and to make sure that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly, and to store your password so you do not have to enter it every time when you visit this site).

**(b) Personal Information**

We also collect certain information that personally identifies you; referred to as "Personal Information", when you visit this site, communicate with us through email, participates in forums, chat groups, bulletin boards, or otherwise complete online forms, contest entries, online surveys etc. This information includes (i) Contact Data (i.e., your name, mailing address, and e-mail address); (ii) Financial Data (i.e. your account or credit card number); and (iii) Demographic Data (i.e., your zip code, country, age, and income). This data is useful for you to access certain premiums, services and to purchase products that we offer via this site.

## 2\. How We Use The Collected Information

**(a) Company Use Of Personal Information**

We use the "Contact Data" to inform you about our company, our products, our services, promotional offers from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary. We use your "Financial Data" to validate your eligibility for certain products or services and to bill you for products and services that you may purchase on this site. We use your "Demographic Data" to personalize your experience on this site and to display customized content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences.

**(b) Sharing of Personal Information**

We share certain pieces of your personal information that we collect from you in the ways described in Section 1(a) and Section 1(b) above. We share "Demographic Data" with advertisers and other third parties only on a non-personally-identifiable basis. We don't share your "Contact Data" with third parties. We share your "Financial Data" only with our business partners who help us in performing certain operations of this site (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, or data storage and security). 

Our business partners have all agreed to follow the same standards of confidentiality that we have described to you in this privacy policy, and they will only use your personal information to perform their specific business obligations to this site. If you do not want us to share your personal information with any third parties, send us an email through our online support system or choose the "opt out" box on our online forms. This act might limit your ability to use all of the features and services we offer on this site. We also provide a process for you to review and request changes to your personal information; this process is described in Section 3(a), below.

**(c) User Choice Regarding Collection, Use, and Distribution of Personal Information**

We provide you full right to allow us or not to disclose your personal information. Even if you don't allow us, you can still access and use much of this site; however, you might not be able to access and use those areas of this site that require your personal information. You can also choose if you want to or if you don't want to receive information and promotional offers from us and from some of our partners.

## 3\. Security of Collected Information

Except as otherwise mentioned in this privacy policy, we will not disclose your personal information to the third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (i) comply with a court order or other legal process; (ii) protect our rights or property; or (iii) enforce our Terms of Service. Your personal information is stored on secure servers and we provide you with the capability to transmit your personal information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser.

**(a) User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information**

We provide a process on your site so that you can confirm that your personal information remains correct and up-to-date. You may modify or update your personal profile at [insert link here] by logging into this site and accessing your personal profile. Through your personal profile you may: (i) review and update you personal information that we have already collected; (ii) choose whether or not you want us to send you information about our company and promotional offers from some of our partners; and/or (iii) choose whether or not you want us to disclose your personal information with third parties.

**(b) Lost, Misused, or Stolen Information**

If your user name, passwords or credit card is stolen, lost or used without your permission; you should inform us immediately. We will remove that information from your account and update our records accordingly.

**(c) Public Information**

This site contains links to other websites. If you visit those sites by clicking those links; we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such websites. This site also has forums, chat rooms, bulletin boards, forums and message boards, and news groups; and any information that you disclose in those areas is considered as "public information". We are not responsible over its use or misuse and you should be careful about disclosing your personal information to any of those areas.

## 4\. Change in Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update, modify or change our privacy policy anytime without any prior or subsequent notification to you. Any such change will become immediately effective as we update our privacy policy on this page. We encourage you to re-read our privacy policy from time to time so that you are aware of any changes that we may make. 

## 5\. Contact

Should you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, feel free to contact us immediately via our online support system.
